namestall.com 2018-05-15

# Privacy Policy | NameStall

### Privacy Policy

We at NameStall.com ("NameStall") will never sell, rent, exchange, share or otherwise provide your personal information to other people, companies or entities. This applies to all information that you provide through any method of communication with NameStall. As such, your individual information is confidential. Any data that we gather are used by NameStall solely for the purpose of helping us serve you better. NameStall takes your privacy very seriously. We pledge to be as or even more stringent than any laws related to the collection of data while following our own strict policies and standards.

### Membership Data

Once you have signed up for our service, you have joined as a member. We only collect and maintain data that has been knowingly given to us by you as a consumer or member. Such data can include, but is not limited to: name and email address. Remember, when you provide or update information, any and all transmission of personal data is done through our secure server and secure server software so that your data is protected. In this way, we encrypt all such transmissions and further protect the data after transmission against unauthorized access in our secure data storage.

### Domain Name Searches & Ideas

We do not share your domain name ideas or domain keyword lists and never register any domains that you have found or selected as potential candidates for registration.

However, we do not also reserve any domain names for our users. If you find available domain names, you are at your own risk to register them as soon as possible.

Only when you share or submit your domain name ideas or suggestions to our [user domain suggestions](http://www.namestall.com/user-domain-suggestions "User Submitted Domain Suggestions") section, we disclose your ideas. And we never register any domain name when a user domain name is in pending condition. Just because of extensive abuse and junk & rubbish [domain name suggestions](http://www.namestall.com/domain-name-suggestions "Domain Name Suggestions") we keep users� domain name suggestions in pending queue (waiting for approval). And we manually check all submitted pending domain names to avoid abuse and maintain quality suggestion list.

### Keyword Statistics

NameStall uses the aggregated keyword data for statistical purposes - for example �1000 Top Words� keywords used during some time period. The keywords in the statistics are never published unless there have been at least several hundred query occurrences.

### Google Keyword Statistics

We manually grab data from google keyword tool for your [high paying keywords](http://www.namestall.com/high-paying-keywords "High Paying Keywords") domain search list. And we do not update those data (like keyword, competition, global monthly search volume, cpc) everyday or frequently. For top popular domain keywords it is same. So data may not match with google�s latest data (as google updates them frequently) sometimes. Please use those data at your own risk.

### Cookies

"Cookies" are minute pieces of information stored via your browser on your computer. These cookies allow sites to learn about the users when they visit specific sites. We only use cookies to personalize your experience on NameStall. When you enter the site, we place a cookie in your browser's cookie folder. This allows us to keep track of the areas you visit on NameStall. In addition, if you so choose, your NameStall membership identification and password are saved in a cookie so that you do not have to sign in each time you visit the site. This is a service we offer entirely for your convenience. We are committed to your privacy, and no individual information that is saved in your cookie file will ever be provided to a third party. We may also monitor your passage through the site in order to improve the overall presentation of the site and your ability to use it. Nonetheless, in no way will we be able to identify you personally, and download, transmit or gain access to your personal information through such monitoring unless you have chosen the option to allow for personalization.

In sum, your security and privacy is of our utmost concern, and we will never intentionally violate the trust you place in us.
